{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
      {
        "question": "พอดีเป๊ะ",
        "correct_answer": "exact",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "install"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "เปลี่ยนยางแบน",
        "correct_answer": "to replace a flat tyre",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "to assess the damage"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ประเมินความเสียหาย",
        "correct_answer": "to assess the damage",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "to assess one's finess"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ทดสอบสมรรถภาพร่างกาย",
        "correct_answer": "to assess one's finess",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "to assess one's strengths and weaknesses"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ประเมิณจุดแข็งและจุดอ่อน",
        "correct_answer": "to assess one's strengths and weaknesses",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "to fix a pipe"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ซ่อมท่อน้ำ",
        "correct_answer": "to fix pipe",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "to replace one's passport"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ซ่อมเฟืองท้ายรถ",
        "correct_answer": "to fix the gears on one's car",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "to fix a broken light"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ทำเล็บ",
        "correct_answer": "to do one's nails",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "to do one's hair"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ดูอาการบาดเจ็บ",
        "correct_answer": "to look at the injury",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "to look at what's causing it"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ดูสิ่งที่ก่อเหตุ",
        "correct_answer": "to look at what's causing it",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "to do one's hair"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ใช้เวลา",
        "correct_answer": "spend time",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "on time"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "พาดหัวข้อ",
        "correct_answer": "headline news",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "business"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "สิ่งแวดล้อม",
        "correct_answer": "environment",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "opinion"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ความคิดเห็น",
        "correct_answer": "opinion",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "polities"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "การเมือง",
        "correct_answer": "polities",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "เหี้ยตู่"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "กำไร",
        "correct_answer": "profit",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "drop"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ลดลง",
        "correct_answer": "drop",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "pilot"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "นัดกันหยุดงาน",
        "correct_answer": "to go on strike",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "peace"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ความสงบ",
        "correct_answer": "peace",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "claim"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "การพัฒนา",
        "correct_answer": "breakthrough",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "process"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "อ้าง",
        "correct_answer": "claim",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "hit"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "การบำบัด",
        "correct_answer": "treatment",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "injury"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "อาการบาดเจ็บ",
        "correct_answer": "injury",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "chance"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "โอกาส",
        "correct_answer": "chance",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "scandal"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "เรื่องอื้อฉาว",
        "correct_answer": "scandal",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "hit"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "โจมตี",
        "correct_answer": "hit",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "government"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "หวังดีเสมอ",
        "correct_answer": "to hit the team's hopes",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "found guilty of "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ตัดสินมีความผิด",
        "correct_answer": "found guilty of ",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "to decide a sentence"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ตัดสินจำคุก",
        "correct_answer": "to decide a sentence",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "union"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "สหภาพแรงงาน",
        "correct_answer": "union",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "staff"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "กำจัด",
        "correct_answer": "to get rid of",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "to keep out of "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "แนะนำ",
        "correct_answer": "advised",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "president"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ถอยออกห่าง",
        "correct_answer": "to keep out of",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "move on"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ยารักษาโรค",
        "correct_answer": "drug",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "disease"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "โรคภัย",
        "correct_answer": "disease",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "outright"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ทันที",
        "correct_answer": "outright",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "weather"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ซีด",
        "correct_answer": "pale",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "nasty cut"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "รอยแผลเป็น",
        "correct_answer": "nasty cut",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "stiff"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "แข็งทื่อ",
        "correct_answer": "stiff",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "ache"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "เจ็บปวด",
        "correct_answer": "ache",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "injured"
        ]
      }
    ]
}